# **Camille Dunning**

949-395-6217 | adunning@ucsd.edu | Belmont, CA 94002 | https://camille-004.github.io

#### **SUMMARY**

Forward-thinking data science intern with background working effectively in dynamic environments. Fluent in Python and Java programming languages used to develop Al-driven solutions and researching optimal machine learning methodologies. Proud team player focused on achieving project objectives with speed and accuracy.

#### **SKILLS**

- Advanced mathematical abilities
- SQL expert
- Python
- Deep Learning
- Reinforcement Learning and Deep Q-Learning
- R + Scala
- API Design
- Git version control
- Java
- Web frameworks

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Founder, Flocure, November 2020-Current

Belmont, CA

- Led organization, established business direction and actualized operational plans to meet goals.
- Adopting and improving current NLP and CV methods to create an application that will alleviate manual work in studying and memorization

NLP Intern, Blooma, December 2020-Current

#### San Diego, CA

- Leveraged Python and machine learning pipelines to extract key information from lending documents, converted into a FastAPI.
- Reduced time for labeling and processing procedure from weeks to seconds

# Undergraduate Student Researcher, Qualcomm Institute, January 2021-Current La Jolla, CA

• Leveraging influxes of data and contributing to the development QI's college return on investment app

#### Data Science Intern, BD, March 2020-Current

San Diego, CA

- Research concentrating on drug diversion and enterprise medication inventory optimization.
- Use deep learning, ML flow, data visualization, and reinforcement learning to analysis new data sources as well as automating existing capabilities.

### Summer Research Intern, Scripps Research Translational Institute, May 2020-August 2020 La Jolla, CA

• Compiled, entered and modeled data to help researchers understand and interpret the synchrony between vital signs during the incubation period (Ebola, Margburg, among other diseases) using signal dynamics.

## Data Science Intern, iSchemaView, April 2019-September 2019

#### San Mateo, CA

- Extracted metadata from datastores, normalized, and vectorized CT perfusion images into corresponding color "stacks"
- Investigated and implemented clustering algorithms to characterize CTP artifacts

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

Bachelor of Science

#### Data Science, University Of California - San Diego, La Jolla CA Expected in December 2022

- Halicioglu Data Science Institute Industry-Sponsored Research Scholarship Recipient
- Halicioglu Data Science Institute Undergraduate Research Scholarship Recipient
- Provost Honors (awarded to students with a 3.5+ GPA on a given quarter)
- Completed coursework in Graph Theory, Statistics and Data Structures
- IEEE Project Drive Reinforcement Learning Engineer
- Data Science Student Society Online Content Co-Director
- UI/UX designer and back-end developer for Project E-Cell Organization
- Data Science Alliance Data Visualization Competition Winner
- Minor in Mathematics